ZAHRA ATAEI

Nutritionist and Dietitian

@ zataei7474@gmail.com in Zahra Ataei

**** +46 73-780 35 46 O AtaHealth

Stockholm, Sweden



SUMMARY

I am an enthusiastic dietitian with more than five years of education and experience in nutrition and dietetics. Currently studying Master's in Nutrition Science at Karolinska Institutet.

I have helped patients with various health problems. This experience has given me the ability to think critically to deal with different situations. I work based on scientific evidence, and I am skilled at consulting people to have healthy lifestyles. Reliability and having a great sense of responsibility are my strengths at work.

EXPERIENCE

Nutrition Coach

at social media

Jul, 2020 - Ongoing

Stockholm, Sweden

As I have concerns about public health issues, especially in developing counties, I have created social media pages to inform, consult, and inspire people to have healthy eating habits and lifestyles. My page on Instagram now has more than 10,000 followers, mostly Persian-speaking living around the world.

Dietitian

at Munesi gym

Mov, 2017 - Nov, 2018

▼ Tehran, Iran

I worked there as a dietitian and consultant for beginners and professional trainers as well as obese and overweight people.

Dietitian

at Freelance

₩ Sep, 2016 - Oct, 2017

▼ Tehran, Iran

I have worked independently with pregnant and nursing mothers, overweight people, and those with metabolic syndrome as a part-time job. I worked online and was able to assist many individuals in improving their health.

EDUCATION

Masters' in Nutrition Science

at Karolinska Institutet

Aug, 2021 - Ongoing

Stockholm, Sweden

Bachelors' in Nutrition and Dietetics

Completed my bachelor's thesis on the association between spiritual health and the level of pain in cancer patients referred to the chemotherapy section (a cross-sectional study).

SKILLS

Flexibility and adaptability

Communication

Microsoft PowerPoint

Nutrition coaching

Lifestyle intervention

Diet management

Collaboration with other healthcare professionals

Nutrition status assessment

Nutrition needs assessment

LANGUAGES

Swedish: C1

English: B2

Persian: Native

INTERNSHIPS

various departments

at Shahid Beheshti Hospital

may, 2017 - May, 2018

- Hospital's food department
- Medical diagnostic laboratory
- · Children's disease department
- · Health center
- · Liver, Digestive and Pancreatic Department
- Cardiovascular CCU Department
- · Department of Diabetes and Endocrinology
- · Surgery and ICU
- · Kidney department
- · The food industry and municipalities

I have passed all the practices with good grades.

REFERENCES

Dr. Zatollah Asemi (Professor)

from Kashan University of Medical Sciences

e-post: asemi_r@yahoo.com

HOBBIES

Exercise
Cycling
Traveling
Camping
Hiking
Blogging
Baking and cooking
Listening to podcasts
Reading books
Reading scientific articles